Guide to the Robert F. Curl Academic papers, 1953- 2012, bulk 1985-1993 MS 483
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
Robert F. Curl academic papers
1953-2012
1981-1995
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas https://library.rice.edu/woodson
Curl, Robert F.
MS 483
23 Linear Feet (31 boxes, one oversize item in annex)
The collection holds the chemistry research materials during a portion of Dr. Robert Curl's tenure at Rice University through 2012. The materials, arranged chronologically, include typescript copies, proofs, notes, charts, correspondence and reprints regarding published and unfinished research. Also contains information relating to Curl's positions on non-Rice boards and committees.
Biographical Note
Robert F. Curl's affiliation with Rice University begins with his bachelor's degree at Rice in 1954. He received his Ph.D. in 1957 at the University of California, Berkeley. After a year at Harvard University as a research fellow in microwave spectroscopy, Curl joined the Rice faculty as an assistant professor in chemistry. In 1967 he became a full professor, served as chair of the chemistry department from 1992-1996, and then as the Harry C. and Olga K. Wiess Professor of Natural Sciences. In 2002, Curl was named the first Pitzer Professor of Chemistry.
Curl has received many honors and awards including the Clayton Prize of the Institute of Mechanical Engineers and the Alexander von Humboldt Senior US Scientist Award from the University of Bonn, Germany. Along with Richard Smalley (Rice University's Gene and Norman Hackerman Professor of Chemistry) and Sir Harold Kroto (University of Sussex, Brighton, England), Curl received the 1996 Nobel Prize in Chemistry for the discovery in 1985 of buckminsterfullernes, the third molecular form of carbon. In 1992 the trio received the American Physical Society International Prize for New Materials.
Curl is a member of Phi Beta Kappa, Phi Lamba Upsilon and Sigma Xi, and a Fellow of the Optical Society of America. He has been Visiting Research Officer at the National Research Council of Canada, visiting scientist at the Institute of Molecular Science, Okazaki, Japan, and the National Institute for Standards and Technology in Boulder, the University of Bonn, and the University of Canterbury, Christchurch, New Zealand.
Scope and Contents
The collection holds the chemistry research materials during a portion of Curl's tenure at Rice University through 2012. The materials, arranged chronologically, include typescript copies, proofs, notes, charts, correspondence and reprints regarding published and unfinished research. The collection also holds various items relating to Curl's positions on a number of Non-Rice boards and committees.
Access Restrictions
This material is open for research.
Conditions Governing Access
Stored offsite at the Library Service Center and require 24-hour notice for retrieval. Please contact the Woodson Research Center at 713-348-2586 or woodson@rice.edu for more information.
Acquisition Information
Received by the Woodson Research Center on Oct. 16, 1999, and officially gifted to Rice University by Robert F. Curl on Dec. 9, 1999. Additional materials were donated in 2010 and 2018.
Related Material
See also Robert Curl, Richard Smalley, Buckyball information (vertical) files, and [Rice] Nobel Prize Collection record group.
Index Terms
Subjects
Microwave spectroscopy; Buckminsterfullerene; Chemistry; Nobel prizes; Chemistry -- Experiments; Universities and colleges
Document Types
corrrespondence; charts (graphic documents); typescripts; notes
Subjects (Persons)
Curl, Robert F.
Subjects (Corporations)
Rice University; Rice University. Department of Chemistry
- Series I: Research publications 1981-1984
  - High Resolution Study of the O-H Stretch Fundamental of Methanol, research notes, charts, printouts, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Methanol research, notes, printouts, charts, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Observation of the Transition of the Br Atom by Color Center Laser Spectroscopy, Chemical Physics Letters, reprint, printouts, Jan. 1981 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Experimental Excitation of a Transition State in a Chemical Reaction, typescript copy, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Kinetic Spectroscopy with the Color Center Laser, Proceedings of the International Conference on Lasers '83, typescript copy, reprints, notes, Dec. 1983 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Chemiluminescent Channels Opened by Photon Absorption During Reactive Collisions, Proceedings of the Conference on Atomic and Molecular Collisions in a Laser Field, typescript copy, copyright, March 1984 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The far-infrared laser magnetic resonance spectrum of the SiH radical and determination of ground state parameters, Journal of Chemical Physics, notes, typescript copies, Oct. 1984 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Sensitivity improvement of tone-burst modulated spectroscopy with a color-center laser, Journal of the Optical Society of America B, reprint, notes, typescript copy, corresp., printouts, transparencies, Oct. 1984 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Color Center Laser Spectroscopy of Transient Species Produced by Excimer Laser Flash Photolysis, Journal of the Optical Society of America, corresp., typescript copy, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Series II: Research publications 1985
  - Rotational analysis of the system of C Journal of Chemical Physics, reprint, corresp., typescript copy, printouts, April 1985 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Rotational analysis… revisions, printouts, notes, corresp., 1985 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Rotational analysis… erratum, reprint, notes, printouts, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Color center laser kinetic spectroscopy: observation of the ΔNH vibrational fundamental, Journal of the Optical Society of America, proof, reprint, typescript copy, notes, printouts, May 1985 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - The Microwave and Far-Infrared Spectra of the SiH Radical, The Astrophysical Journal, copyright, reprints, May 1985 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Rotational analysis of the System of C Journal of Chemical Physics, reprint, typescript copies, corresp., charts, printouts, Oct. 1985 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - C Buckminsterfullerene, Nature, reprints, proofs, Nov. 1985 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Magnetic Rotation Observation of the C Transition Using a Color Center Laser, Journal of Molecular Spectroscopy, reprints, printouts, corresp., notes, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Lanthanum Complexes of Spheroidal Carbon Shells, Journal of the American Chemical Society, reprint, typescript copy, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Laser Magnetic Resonance Spectrum of the band of NCO, typescript copy, notes, charts, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Semiconductor cluster beams: One and two color ionization studies of Si and Ge Journal of Chemical Physics, typescript copy, reprints, notes, corresp., Dec. 1985 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Supersonic III-V Semiconductor Cluster Beams: Ga Journal of Chemical Physics, typescript copy, proof, corresp., 1985 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Series III: Research publications 1986-1987
  - Photoexcitation of Reaction Complexes in the Reaction K+NaCl→KCl+Na, Journal of Chemical Physics, notes, reports, corresp., typescript copy, July 1986 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Studies of the NH+NO Reaction by Infrared Kinetic Spectroscopy, Journal of Physical Chemistry, notes, reprint, typescript copy, May 1986 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Reactivity of Large Carbon Clusters: Spheroidal Carbon Shells and Their Possible Relevance to the Formation and Morphology of Soot, Journal of Physical Chemistry, reprint, typescript copy, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Negative Carbon Cluster Ion Beams: New Evidence for the Special Nature of C Chemical Physics Letters, reprint, copyright, typescript copy, May 1986 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Observation of the laser-assisted reaction K+NaCl+H→Na*+KCl using K atoms selected by a hexapole magnetic field, Physical Review A, reprint, notes, typescript copy, Nov. 1986 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Photodetachment and photofragmentation studies of semiconductor cluster anions, Journal of Chemical Physics, reprint, corresp., copyright, typescript copy, notes, report, proof, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - A Reply to `Magic Numbers in Cn+ and Cn- Abaundance Distributions Based on Experimental Observations, Chemical Physics Letters, copyright, notes, printouts, typescript copy, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Color Center Laser Spectroscopy of Vibrationally Excited C2H, Journal of Chemical Physics, notes, reprint, corresp., proof, typescript copy, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Multiwavenumber linearized diode laser spectra by overlapping frequency scans, Applied Optics, corresp., charts, proof, typescript copy, Jan. 1987 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Color Center Laser Spectoscopy of C2H and C2D, Journal of Molecular Spectroscopy, reprint, typescript copy, notes, proof, printouts, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Infrared Kinetic Spectroscopy Using a Color-Center Laser, Spectroscopy, reprint, typescript copy, charts, proof, March 1987 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Long Carbon Chain Molecules in Circumstellar Shells, The Astrophysical Journal, reprint, March 1987 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - The UV absorption spectrum of C60 (buckminsterfullerene): A narrow band at 3860 A, Journal of Chemical Physics, reprint, corresp., reports, typescript copy, Oct. 1987 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Rate Constant Measurements of Reactions of C2H with H2O2, C2H2 and NO Using Color Center Laser Kinetic Spectroscopy, Journal of Physical Chemistry, corresp., typescript copy, copyright, charts, notes, proofs, Dec. 1987 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Carbon Condensation, reprint, typescript copy, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Series IV: Research publications 1988-1989
  - Photophysics of buckminsterfullerene and other carbon cluster ions, Journal of Chemical Physics, reprint, notes, typescript copy, corresp., proof, Jan. 1988 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Photodissasociation of semiconductor positive cluster ions, Journal of Chemical Physics, reprint, charts, proofs, typescript copy, Feb. 1988 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Infrared flash kinetic spectroscopy of HCO, Journal of Chemical Physics, reprint, corresp., notes, charts, printouts, proof, typescript copy, Feb. 1988 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - HCO fits, printouts, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Unbiased Least-Squares Fitting of Lower States, Journal of Molecular Spectroscopy, reprint, printouts, proof, typescript copy, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Probing C60, Science, reprint, proof, corresp, notes, typescript copy, Nov. 1988 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Infrared Kinetic Spectroscopy of C2H and C2D, Journal of Molecular Structure, reprint, charts, notes, typescript copy, corresp., proof, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Absorption Cross-section for the OH Fundamental, typescript copy, notes, corresp., printouts, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Gallium Arsenide Cluster Studies, NICOLS: Ninth International Conference on Laser Spectroscopy, typescript copies, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Reaction Mechanism of C2H+O2 Journal of Physical Chemistry, corresp., proofs, typescript copy, notes, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Ammonia Chemisorption on Gallium Arsenide Clusters, Chemical Physics Letters, copyright, corresp., charts, typescript copy, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Series V: Research publications 1990-1991
  - Thermal DeNOx: No HNO at Room Temperature, Chemical Physics Letters, copyright, corresp., typescript copy, notes, printout, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - The OH Stretching Fundamental of Methanol, Journal of Molecular Structure, typescript copy, notes, charts, corresp., copyright, printouts, reprints, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Infrared Flash Kinetic Spectroscopy of the Ketyl Radical, Chemical Physics Letters, corresp., typescript copy, copyright, charts, reprints, printouts, notes, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Infrared Spectroscopy of Jet-Cooled Transient Molecules,Chemical Physics Letters, typescript copy, copyright, reports, corresp., notes, charts, transparency, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Rate Constant Measurements of C2H with CH4 C2H6, C2H4, D2 and CO, Journal of Physical Chemistry, typescript copy, corresp., reports, proof, notes, copyright, charts, printout, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Observation of structure in transition state spectra of the bimolecular reactions K+XNa→KX+Na (X=Br, Cl), Journal of Chemical Physics, reprint, April 1991 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Cold Molecular Beam Electronic Spectrum of C60 and C70, Journal of Chemical Physics, typescript copy, proof, charts, copyright, corresp., 1991 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Fullerenes: The Third Form of Pure Carbon, Scientific American, typescript copy, corresp., notes, reprint, Oct. 1991 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - C60ΔHf, research notes, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Two Varieties of Cn·Ar+ Chemical Physics Letters, typescript copies, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Infrared Flash Kinetic Spectroscopy of v2 of Ketenyl Radical, Journal of Molecular Spectroscopy, proof, notes, corresp., charts, copyright, printout, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Series VI: Research publications 1992-1993
  - Vibrational relaxation of acetylene produced by the photolysis of vinyl bromide, Journal of Chemical Physics, proof, typescript copy, charts, printout, corresp., reprints, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Continuous-wave infrared laser spectrometer based on difference frequency generation in AgGaS2 for high-resolution spectroscopy, Journal of the Optical Society of America B, reprint, notes, typescript copy, Feb. 1992 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Photoexcitation spectra of transition region species in reactions of potassium with sodium halides, Journal of Chemical Physics, typescript copy, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Optimization of a mid-infrared high resolution difference frequency laser spectrometer, Journal of the Optical Society of America B, corresp., typescript copy, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Acetylene Combustion Reactions: Rate Constant Measurements of HCCO with O2 and C2H2 Chemical Physics Letters, typescript copy, reports, copyright, corresp., 1992 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Rotationally Resolved Spectrum of the v1 CH Stretch of the Propargyl Radical, Chemical Physics Letters, typescript copy, notes, corresp., 1992 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Isomers of Gallium Arsenide Cluster Ions, Chemical Physics Letters, corresp., typescript copy, reports, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Mass Spectrometric Studies of the Fullerences, Buckminsterfullerene and Related Carbon Clusters, corresp., typescript copy, copyright, reprint, negatives, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Gallium Arsenide Clusters Etched by NO, Journal of Chemical Physics, corresp., typescript copy, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Pre-1990 Evidence for the Fullerene Proposal, Carbon, corresp., typescript copy, copyright, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Difference-frequency generation in AgGaS2 by using single-mode diode-laser pump sources, Optics Letters, proof, corresp., copyright, typescript copy, July 1993 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Branching Ratio of the Reaction NH2+NO at Elevated Temperatures, Journal of Physical Chemistry, proof, corresp., typescript copy, Aug. 1993 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - The v1 fundamental of HCCN: Evidence for quasilinearity, Chemical Physics Letters, copyright, corresp., charts, typescript copy, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Formation and Chemistry of the Fullerenes, Applied Superconductivity, reprint, corresp., typescript copy, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - On the Formation of the Fullerenes, Philosophical Transactions of the Royal Society of London, Series A, typescript copy, corresp., 1993 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - A Widely Tunable Difference Frequency Source for Infrared Kinetic Spectroscopy, Proceedings of the International Conference on LASERS '92, typescript copy, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Probing Chemical Reaction: Evidence for Exploration of an Excited Potential Energy Surface at Thermal Energies, Science, typescript copy, corresp., report, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Fullerences: Collapse and Growth, Nature, corresp., reports, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - NH2+NO Yields as function of T, typescript copies, notes, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Design Considerations of an Infrared Spectrometer Based on Difference Frequency Generation in AgGaSe2 Applied Optics, reprint, typescript copies, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Branching Ration of the Reaction NH2+NO at Elevated Temperatures, Journal of Physical Chemistry, notes, printouts corresp., reprint, typescript copy, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Series VII: Research publications 1993-1995
  - The Reaction of NH2 with O, Journal of Physical Chemistry, reprint, typescript copy, corresp., June 1994 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Rate Constant Measurement of the Recombination Reaction C3H3+C3H3 Journal of Physical Chemistry, proof, corresp., typescript copy, reports, notes, July 1994 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - CW difference frequency generation using AgGaS2: problems encountered in power scaling, Nonharmonic Optical Frequency Conversion: Parametric Oscillators and Related Devices, typescript copy, corresp., 1994 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Quasi-Linearity in HCCN: Effects on the v2 Fundamental, Festschrift, typescript copy, reprint, copyright, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Detection of CO in air using diode-pumped 4.6 µm difference frequency generation in quasi-phase-matched LiNbO3, Optics Letters, typescript copy, corresp., 1995 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Propargyl from the Reaction of Singlet Methylene with Acetylene, Journal of Physical Chemistry, reprint, corresp., copyright, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Detection of methane in air using diode-laser pumped difference-frequency generation near 3.2 µm, Applied Physics B Lasers and Optics, reprint, corresp., 1995 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Series VIII: Research publications Undated
  - Water/gas modification of thermal DeNOx, [research]: charts, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Difference Frequency Generation in AgGaS2 Using Single-Mode Diode Laser Pump Sources, Optics Letters, typescript copy, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - The Role of Fine Structure States in a Chemical Reaction: Na*+KBr→NaBr+K*, typescript copy, notes, charts, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - A Continuously Tunable Long Wavelength CW IR Source for High-Resolution Spectroscopy and Trace Gas Detection, typescript copies (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Compact tunable difference-frequency sources in the mid-infrared pumped by single-mode diode lasers, typescript, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Compact external cavity differnce-frequency sources in the mid-infrared based on AgGaS2 and diode lasers, typescript copy (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - CW tunable 8/7-µm spectroscopic source pumped by fiber-coupled communications diode lasers, typescript copy, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - High Resolution Diode Laser Spectroscopy of Transient Species, EICOLS, typescript copy (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Diode Laser Kinetic Spectroscopy, typescript copy, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Laser Vaporization of Graphite, reports, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Kinetic Spectroscopy Using a Color Center Laser, Color Center Laser Spectroscopy of Free Radicals, ILS, typescript copies, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Measurement of Nonlinear Coefficient and Phase Matching Characteristics of AgGaS2 Journal of Quantum Electronics, notes, typescript copy (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - CW Difference Frequency Generation in AgGaS2 typescript copies, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Compact external cavity difference-frequency sources in the mid-infrared based on AgGaS2 and diode lasers, typescript copy (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Series IX: Research publications addendum, 1959-1997
  - 1950s
    - Volumetric Thermodynamic Properties of Fluids-Enthalpy, Free Energy, and Entropy, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Microwave Spectrum, Barriet to Internal Rotation, and Structure of Methyl Formate, 1959 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - 1960s
    - Atomic Term Symbols by Group Theory, 1960 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Microwave Specture of O18 Formic Acid and Structure of Formic Acid, 1960 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Microwave Spectrum of Chlorine Dioxide. I. Rotational Assignment, 1961 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Microwave Spectrum of O18 Formyl Fluoride and the Structure of Formyl Fluoride, 1961 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Microwave Spectrum of Chlorine Dioxide. II. Analysis of Hyperfine Structure and the Spectrum of Cl34O16O18, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Microwave Spectrum of Chlorine Dioxide. III. Interpretation of Hyperfine Coupling Constants Obtained in Terms of the Electronic Structure, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Erratum: Microwave Spectrum of Chlorine Dioxide. III. Interpretation of the Hyperfine Coupling Constants Obtained in Terms of the Electronic Structure, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Microwave Spectrum of Methyl Isocyanate, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Dipole Moment of Nitrogen Dioxide, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Equilibrium Conformation of N-Methylene-methylamine from Microwave Data, 1964 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Infrared Spectrum of N-Methylenemethylamine, 1964 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Microwave Spectrum of N-Methyl Methylenimine, 1964 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Microwave Spectrum of Vinyl Formate, 1964 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Microwave Spectrum of NO2: Fine Structure and Magnetic Coupling, 1964 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Microwave Spectrum of Methyl Thionylamine, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Coulomb hole in the ground state of two-electron atoms, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Microwave Spectrum of Methyl Vinyl Ketone, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Microwave Spectrum of SiF2, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Microwave Spectrum of Methyl Azide, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Spin Statistics Isomerization in Methane, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Millimeter-Wavelength Microwave Spectrum of Nitrogen Dioxide, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Microwave Spectrum of 14N16O17O, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Microwave Spectrum, Force Constants, and Structure of SiF2, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Proton Magnetic Resonance Spectrum and Nuclear Overhauser Effects of N-Methylmethylenimine, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Nuclear Spin State Equilibration through Nonmagnetic Collisions, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Infrared Spectrum, Force Constants, and Thermodynamic Functions of SiF2, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Microwave Spectrum of Methyl Vinyl Sulfide, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Microwave Spectrum of Allyl Alcohol, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Thermodynamic Properties from Intensity Measurements in Microwave Spectoscopy, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Dipole Moments of the Sulfides Pb, Sn, and Si from Stark Effect Measurements, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - 1970s
    - Diagnostic Least Squares, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Microwave Spectrum of Chlorine Dioxide. VI. v2=1 State, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Microwave Spectrum of GeF2, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Microwave Spectrum of 2-Aminoethanol: Structural Effects of the Hydrogen Bond, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Microwave Spectrum: Molecular Structure, Force field, and Dipole Moment of Thiocarbonyl Selenide, SCSe, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Microwave Spectrum of s-Trans Acryloyl Chloride, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Microwave Spectrum of Cyclohexene Oxide, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Microwave Spectrum of Salicyl Aldehyde: Structure of the Hydrogen Bond, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Laser Magnetic Resonance Spectrum of NO2 at 33 pm and 311 pm, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Microwave Spectrum of BF2OH, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Microwave Spectrum of GeF2: Quadruple Coupling and Centrifugal Distorion, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Microwave Spectrum and Dipole Moment of Vinyltrifluorosilane, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Microwave spectrum of Salicyl Aldehyde: Structure of the Hydrogen Bond, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Infrared-Radio Frequency Double Resonance Observations of Pure Rotational Q-Branch Transitions of Methane, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Determination of Thermodynamic Functions from Absolute Intensity Measurements in Microwave Spectroscopy, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 3)